JOSH GORDON: Classifiers are only
戈登(Josh Gordon)：分类器的优秀之处
as good as the features you provide.
只在于你所提供的各样不同特性
That means coming up with good features
这意味着具备好的特性
is one of your most important jobs in machine learning.
是你在机器学习里 其中最重要的工作
But what makes a good feature, and how can you tell?
但是什么是好的特性 且你怎么能知道?
If you're doing binary classification,
如果你正在做二分类
then a good feature makes it easy to decide
那么一个好的特性
between two different things.
使它可以很容易在两个 不同的事物之间作决定
For example, imagine we wanted to write a classifier
例如假设我们要撰写一个分类器
to tell the difference between two types of dogs--
用来分辨两种类型的狗
greyhounds and Labradors.
灰猎犬及拉布拉多犬
Here we'll use two features-- the dog's height in inches
在这里我们将使用两个特征 狗狗的身高以英寸为单位
and their eye color.
及它们眼睛的颜色
Just for this toy example, let's make a couple assumptions
用这个玩具作为例子 让我们做一些有关狗的假设
about dogs to keep things simple.
使事情变得简单
First, we'll say that greyhounds are usually
首先我们会说灰猎犬通常
taller than Labradors.
比拉布拉多犬高
Next, we'll pretend that dogs have only two eye
其次我们会假设狗狗的眼睛
colors-- blue and brown.
只有两种颜色—蓝色和棕色
And we'll say the color of their eyes
我们会说它们眼睛的颜色
doesn't depend on the breed of dog.
不是取决于品种
This means that one of these features is useful
这意味着其中的一个特点是有用的
and the other tells us nothing.
而另一个没有告诉我们任何事
To understand why, we'll visualize them using a toy
要理解其中原因 我们将建立一个玩具数据集
dataset I'll create.
使其可视化
Let's begin with height.
我们从身高开始
How useful do you think this feature is?
你们认为这个特点有何作用?
Well, on average, greyhounds tend
平均而言灰猎犬
to be a couple inches taller than Labradors, but not always.
往往比拉布拉多犬高几英寸 但并非总是如此
There's a lot of variation in the world.
在世界上有很多不同的变异
So when we think of a feature, we
当我们想到一个特性时
have to consider how it looks for different values
必须考虑它怎样在一个种群中
in a population.
寻找不同的值
Let's head into Python for a programmatic example.
以Python程式为例
I'm creating a population of 1,000
我创建了一个1000只狗的种群
dogs-- 50-50 greyhound Labrador.
50-50 灰猎犬-拉布拉多犬
I'll give each of them a height.
每一只狗我也会给它一个身高
For this example, we'll say that greyhounds
在这个例子中我们会说
are on average 28 inches tall and Labradors are 24.
灰猎犬的平均身高为28英寸 而拉布拉多犬身高为24英寸
Now, all dogs are a bit different.
现在所有狗狗都有点不同
Let's say that height is normally distributed,
身高是正态分布
so we'll make both of these plus or minus 4 inches.
然后我们会给它们加或减4英寸
This will give us two arrays of numbers,
我们将会得到两个数字阵列
and we can visualize them in a histogram.
然后利用矩形图使其可视化
I'll add a parameter so greyhounds are in red
我将会添加一个参数 灰猎犬是红色
and Labradors are in blue.
拉布拉多犬为蓝色
Now we can run our script.
现在我们可以运行脚本
This shows how many dogs in our population have a given height.
这样显示出一个给定的身高有多少只狗
There's a lot of data on the screen,
在屏幕上有很多的数据
so let's simplify it and look at it piece by piece.
让我们将其简化 逐个阅读
We'll start with dogs on the far left
我们从最左边的狗狗开始
of the distribution-- say, who are about 20 inches tall.
它们身高大约都是20英寸
Imagine I asked you to predict whether a dog with his height
想象一下 如果我请大家预测 这样身高的狗狗是一只
was a lab or a greyhound.
拉布拉多犬还是灰猎犬
What would you do?
你会怎么做?
Well, you could figure out the probability of each type
你们可以断定在特定的身高
of dog given their height.
每种类型狗狗的概率
Here, it's more likely the dog is a lab.
在这里它较可能是 一只拉布拉多犬
On the other hand, if we go all the way
另一方面
to the right of the histogram and look
如果我们看看柱状图的右面
at a dog who is 35 inches tall, we
看看身高35英寸的狗狗
can be pretty confident they're a greyhound.
我们相当有信心这是一只灰猎犬
Now, what about a dog in the middle?
现在中间的狗狗又怎么样?
You can see the graph gives us less information
你可以看到图表给我们较少信息
here, because the probability of each type of dog is close.
每种类型的狗狗的概率很接近
So height is a useful feature, but it's not perfect.
因此身高是一个有用的特征 但它并不完美
That's why in machine learning, you almost always
所以在机器学习里
need multiple features.
你们总是需要多种的特征
Otherwise, you could just write an if statement
否则你们只是撰写一个if语句
instead of bothering with the classifier.
而不是分类器
To figure out what types of features you should use,
要断定使用哪个特点
do a thought experiment.
就需要做一个假想实验
Pretend you're the classifier.
假设你是一个分类器
If you were trying to figure out if this dog is
你要弄清楚这是一只
a lab or a greyhound, what other things would you want to know?
拉布拉多犬还是灰猎犬 你还想知道什么信息呢?
You might ask about their hair length,
你可能会问它们的头发长度
or how fast they can run, or how much they weigh.
它们跑得多快 或者它们的体重是多少
Exactly how many features you should use
到底应该使用多少特性
is more of an art than a science,
是一门艺术而不是一门科学
but as a rule of thumb, think about how many you'd
但作为一个经验法则 想想你需要多少特征
need to solve the problem.
来解决问题
Now let's look at another feature like eye color.
现在我们看另一特征 例如眼睛的颜色
dogs have only two eye colors, blue and brown.
我们假设狗狗的眼睛 只有两种颜色—蓝色和棕色
And let's say the color of their eyes
我们假定眼睛的颜色
doesn't depend on the breed of dog.
并不取决于狗的品种
Here's what a histogram might look like for this example.
像这样的例子可以用下面矩形图表示
For most values, the distribution is about 50/50.
对于大部分数值，分布大约是50/50
So this feature tells us nothing,
所以这个特征 没有告诉我们任何有用信息
because it doesn't correlate with the type of dog.
因为它跟狗狗的类型没有关联
Including a useless feature like this in your training
假设训练数据内包含 一个像这样无用的特征
data can hurt your classifier's accuracy.
能破坏分类器的准确度
That's because there's a chance they might appear useful purely
因为很有可能
You also want your features to be independent.
你还希望各样特征是独立的
And independent features give you
独立特征给你
different types of information.
不同类型的信息
Imagine we already have a feature-- height and inches--
试想一下我们已经有一个特征 在我们的数据集里—
in our dataset.
身高及英寸
Ask yourself, would it be helpful
问问你自己 如果增加 另一个特征会有所帮助吗
if we added another feature, like height in centimeters?
例如用多少厘米表示身高?
No, because it's perfectly correlated with one
没有用 因为它跟已有的特征
we already have.
密切相关
It's good practice to remove highly correlated features
从训练数据删除高度相关的特征
from your training data.
这是很好的做法
That's because a lot of classifiers
因为很多分类器
aren't smart enough to realize that height in inches
没有足够的智能明白
in centimeters are the same thing,
用厘米或英寸量度身高 是同样的事情
so they might double count how important this feature is.
因此它们可能会重复 计算特征的重要性
Last, you want your features to be easy to understand.
最后你们或者希望特征很容易被理解
For a new example, imagine you want
用一个新的例子
to predict how many days it will take
假如你把一封信从一个城市寄到另一个城市
to mail a letter between two different cities.
你预测需要多少天
The farther apart the cities are, the longer it will take.
两个城市之间的距离越远 所需时间也就越长
A great feature to use would be the distance
一个有用的特征是
between the cities in miles.
用英里表示两个城市之间的距离
A much worse pair of features to use
一个较差的特征就是
would be the city's locations given by their latitude
使用城市的经度及纬度
and longitude.
去标示其位置
And here's why.
这就是其原因
I can look at the distance and make
我可以看看距离
a good guess of how long it will take the letter to arrive.
然后猜测要多久 信件才会到达目的地
But learning the relationship between latitude, longitude,
但是知道经纬度及时间之间的关联后
and time is much harder and would require many more
也很难猜测有关时间
examples in your training data.
并需要更多有关训练数据的例子
Now, there are techniques you can
现在你需要使用不同技巧来断定
use to figure out exactly how useful your features are,
到底哪个特征为何对你有帮助
and even what combinations of them are best,
甚至哪样的组合是最好的
so you never have to leave it to chance.
那么你不再需要听天由命
We'll get to those in a future episode.
我们在下一节再讨论
Coming up next time, we'll continue building our intuition
接下来的时间我们将会继续
for supervised learning.
为监督式学习建立直觉
We'll show how different types of classifiers
我们将会展示怎样使用 不同类型的分类器
can be used to solve the same problem and dive a little bit
来解决同样的问题
deeper into how they work.
并深入了解它们怎样运作
Thanks very much for watching, and I'll see you then.
谢谢收看 我们下次再见